// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Which of the following is a network service?",
    answer: "All",
    options: [
      "File Service",
      "Print Service",
      "Message Service",
      "All"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "The computer that acts as a central authority in a network.",
    answer: "Server",
    options: [
      "Protocol",
      "Client",
      "Server",
      "None"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which of the following is not a connector?",
    answer: "POP",
    options: [
      "BNC",
      "DIX",
      "RJ-45",
      "POP"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "The topology which has a circular loop of point to point links is...",
    answer: "Ring",
    options: [
      "Ring",
      "Bus",
      "Star",
      "Tree"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Two way connection media is ...",
    answer: "Internet",
    options: [
      "Radio",
      "TV",
      "Newspaper",
      "Internet"
    ]
  },
  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

    {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Which is the example of communication media?",
    answer: "All",
    options: [
      "Radio Wave",
      "Fibre Optics",
      "Microwaves",
      "All"
    ]
  },
    
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Choose the odd one out.",
    answer: "PS/2",
    options: [
      "ST connector",
      "BNC",
      "RJ-45",
      "PS/2"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "The topology which has only one true point to point design.",
    answer: "Ring",
    options: [
      "Star",
      "Ring",
      "Mesh",
      "Bus"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "A device which has multiple ports.",
    answer: "Hub",
    options: [
      "Hub",
      "Router",
      "Bridge",
      "Gateway"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Data transfer rate in MODEM is",
    answer: "Bps",
    options: [
      "kbps",
      "Mbps",
      "Bps",
      "None"
    ]
  },
  // {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },
    
    
    
    
];